原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     VioletCheng  二糯米  屯栗子
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第七集
多谢照顾
Thanks for hosting.
过夜怎么样
How was the sleepover?
他俩都喝了5小时能量饮料和一大罐能多益
They each had a 5-Hour Energy drink and a jar of Nutella
然后看了一整晚俄罗斯的行车记录仪录像
and then watched Russian dashcam videos all night.
开车就是杀人
Vodit' znachit ubivat'!
听着  马姬
Listen, Marge.
柯克和我每年都在哥斯达黎加租一栋豪华别墅
Every year, Kirk and I rent a luxury villa in Costa Rica
然后邀请几个精选的家庭跟我们一起
and invite a few select families to join us.
你可能听说过
Maybe you've heard about it?
我一直做梦都想被邀请去参加旅行
I've always dreamed of being invited on this trip,
现在终于要实现了
and now it's about to happen.
表现要拽  马姬  只有你能去的样子
Play it cool, Marge, like only you can.
我看看
Let me see.
哥斯达黎加
Costa Rica...
不行  不行
Nope, nope.
不好意思  第一次听说
Sorry, it's news to me.
我们想问问  你家有没有兴趣
We were wondering, would your family
加入我们呢
be interested in joining us?
你什么时候需要答复
When would you need an answer by?
越快越好
Oh, the sooner the better.
哥斯达黎加
Costa Rica!
是时候一起摇
Time to rock and...
哥斯达黎加
Costa Rica!
哥斯达黎加  哥斯达黎加  哥斯达黎加
Costa Rica! Costa Rica! Costa Rica...!
哥斯达黎加
Costa Rica.
家庭会议
Family meeting!
全体到位
Right now!
范浩腾一家邀请我们
The Van Houtens invited us
参加他们超高端的多家庭旅行
on their super-exclusive multi-family vacation
去哥斯达黎加
to Costa Rica!
我们会待在沙滩上的奢华别墅里
We'll stay in a luxury villa right on the beach...
就在原始雨林旁边
...near pristine rain forests,
那里是地球上百分之五的物种的家
home to five percent of the species on Earth...
生物多样性
Biodiversity!
那里的孩子完全可以带着弯刀
...in a land where it's normal for kids to carry machetes.
快点合法化
Legalize it!
你可以嚼这本指南书
And you can chew on the guidebook.
我总是做梦想成为那种
I've always dreamed of being the kind of family
别的家庭愿意和我们相处的家庭
that other families would be willing to do things with.
哥斯达黎加
Costa Rica!
-哥斯达黎加  -机场美食广场
- Costa Rica! - Airport food court!
-机场美食广场  -哥斯达黎加
- Airport food court! - Costa Rica!
《哥斯达黎加的树蛙》
这才是永远不会停下的鼓膜
Now, that's a tympanic membrane that just won't quit.
等一下  这趟旅行要花掉多少来着
Whoa. This trip's gonna cost how much?
我知道很贵
I know it's expensive,
但我们一辈子都在担心钱
but we spend our whole lives worrying about money.
因为我们没钱
That's because we don't have that much.
我们有按揭  反向抵押借款
We have a mortgage, a reverse mortgage.
我觉得房子其实是车子的
I think the house is owned by the car.
生活就是有关经历
Life is about experiences.
看看这张希伯特一家去年旅行的照片
Look at this photo the Hibberts posted from last year's trip.
再看看我都发了什么
Now look at my feed.
没错
Yeah.
天哪
Oh, boy.
我想要一张我们在瀑布那边的照片
I want a photo of you and me by that waterfall.
能踏上这趟旅行的可能性是我允许
The hope of going on this trip is the only reason
巴仔和苗浩斯成为朋友的唯一理由
I've allowed Bart to stay friends with Milhouse.
现在我可明白一切了
Now I understand everything.
侯默  我知道这挺紧张的
Homie, I know it's a stretch,
但如果柯克和露安可以承担
but if Kirk and Luann can afford it...
就是啊  他赚不到那么多钱
Yeah. He can't earn that much.
他的工作是拖走无上衣女仆面包车
His job is moving the Topless Maids van
这样他们就不用被罚款
so they don't get parking tickets.
我们就疯狂一次  希望一切都好
Let's have one damn fling and hope everything will be okay.
晓得不  你是对的
You know what? You are right.
我不想做婚姻中负责的那个人了
I am sick of being the responsible one in this marriage.
咱们好好活一把
Let's live life.
记着  只要我们拥有彼此
Remember, we can never be poor
咱就不穷
as long as we have each other.
不  我们会穷的
Oh... yes, we can.
我们不如呆在家里
You know, what if we stayed home
拼一幅哥斯达黎加的拼图
and just did puzzles of Costa Rica?
这趟旅行听着真的很贵
I mean, this trip sounds really expensive.
-根本不贵  -瞎说啥呢
- No, not really. - What? No!
让大人操心大人的事儿吧  好吗
You just let the grown-ups worry about grown-up things, okay?
你老爸老妈
Your mom and dad
完美掌控着我们的财政未来
have our financial future all under control.
瞧  免费券
Ooh! Free ticket!
富人更富
The rich get richer!
多家庭旅行
Ah, the multi-family vacation.
瞧瞧有哪些人
Let's see who we've got.
范浩腾一家  当然了  希伯特一家
The Van Houtens, of course. The Hibberts.
丘督学和他的女儿
Superintendent Chalmers and his daughter.
不敢相信我爸爸竟然我把我们分开
I can't believe my father is tearing us apart
整整一周
for a whole week.
宝贝  飞行过程很长
Sweetie, it's a very long flight.
怎么不省着点电
Why don't you save your phone battery.
你在乎的就是这点电吗
All you care about is batteries!
你从来就没爱过
You've never been in love.
我和你的妈妈有过一段非常
Your mother and I had a very...
算了
Never mind.
好了  这里的每一个人
Yep, not one person here
我都不介意和他们度过漫长的时间
I'd mind spending an extended period of time with.
我没时间脱毛  所以就在飞机上解决吧
I didn't have time to wax, so I'll do it on the plane.
那玩意儿来这干什么
What the hell is that doing here?
警察阿卢和他的姐姐本来准备要来
Well, Lou the cop and his sister were gonna go,
但是他被广告牌砸到了
but a billboard fell on him
她的风铃店被烧了
and her wind chime store burned down.
所以我推荐了帕蒂和她的新女朋友
So I suggested Patty and her new girlfriend.
你故意瞒着我
You deliberately hid this from me
现在退出也来不及了
until it was too late to back out.
-是的  -别想否认
- Yes. - Don't try to deny it.
帕蒂的新感情关系一定要有结果
Patty's new relationship really has to work out,
因为约会软件都不肯让她上了
because the dating apps won't take her anymore.
我只需要你对她们好点就行了
All I ask is that you're nice to them.
伊芙琳  这是我的丈夫侯默
Evelyn, this is my husband Homer.
非常礼貌地跟你问好  女士
A very polite hello to you, madam.
看啊看啊  侯默·辛普森
Well, well, Homer Simpson.
我听过好多关于你的事情
I've heard so much about you.
你当然听过了  但是我要为自己辩解
Surely you have, but in my defense,
在私家的旋转木马上小便
urinating on a privately owned merry-go-round
不是随地小便
is not public urination.
多家庭度假航班
好了  谁想喝鸡尾酒
Okay, who wants Miguelitos?
我应该提醒一下新来的
Now, I should warn the newbies--
这些对你们来说一定非常真实
these will seem very authentic to you.
这就是装在杯子里的"纯生"
This stuff is pura vida in a glass.
什么是"纯生"
What's pura vida?
就是纯粹的生活的意思
Uh, it means "pure life."
算是这里的一种心态吧
Kind of a state of mind down here.
非常平静
Very chill.
比你想象的平静
Like what you think of as chill
再平静个一百万倍
but, like, a million times chiller.
老侯  我觉得我体验到了
Homie, I think I'm having an experience.
每次水果与美酒的碰撞  神奇的假期就诞生了
Every time a fruit meets a booze, a magic vacation is born.
你可以试一下
Well, you can try.
天啊  我都不知道
Oh, boy, I didn't know that.
太真实了
So true.
罗德里戈  罗德里戈  我的朋友
Rodrigo, Rodrigo, mi hermano,
把账算在这上面
put the bill on this.
没有什么比大家分摊更像纯粹的生活了
Nothing is less pura vida than check-splitting.
这趟旅行我预付所有的费用
On this trip I pay for everything up front--
食物  别墅的租金
food, the villa rental,
云林谋杀之谜
cloud forest murder mystery--
付款账目
我全都记录在这
and I keep track of 'em right here.
我们到最后的时候再算
Then we settle up at the end.
牧翁·布兰丁斯今晚
Smokey Blandings is putting on
展现出了教科书般的沙包洞技术
a cornhole clinic tonight.
沙包洞
邀请赛
这是真正开始疲劳的时候  吉姆
And this is where fatigue really sets in, Jim.
你扔出第四个沙包的时候
When you're tossing that fourth beanbag,
肌肉都要尖叫了
your muscles are screaming, son.
真是个好日子
Good heavenly days!
你也在追职业沙包洞巡回赛
You also follow the pro cornhole tour?
当然了  我之前在我爸爸的农场里玩
Sure do. I used to play on my daddy's farm.
我们一整天都在扔沙包
We'd toss bags all day,
就算比烫手的山芋还热的时候也不例外
even when it was hotter than a two-dollar pistol.
那的确很热
That is hot.
你说话一直都这么有南部色彩吗
Do you always speak in such colorful Southern-isms?
负鼠妈妈会错过星期天礼拜吗
Does a mama possum skip church on Sundays?
我猜她会的
I bet she does.
侯默  把你的手机收起来
Homer, put your phone away.
伊芙琳  别这样
Evelyn, please.
伊芙琳  你不想和我们一起去购物吗
Evelyn, you don't want to go shopping with us?
这是在度假  宝贝
It's a vacation, sugar bear.
我们就该像被丢掉的拖鞋一样躺在沙滩上
We should be lying on the beach like a lost flip-flop.
但是亲爱的  在沙滩上除了喝酒无事可做
But, darling, there's nothing to do at the beach except drink.
这样吧  你们两个去逛逛
You know what? Why don't you two take in the sights
我带着你的南部情人去沙滩上
while I chaperone your Southern señorita to the beach?
天啊  真是个优雅的解决方案
Well, my, my, what an elegant solution.
我猜这样所有人都能开心了
Well, I guess this way everyone's happy.
今晚的晚餐棒极了  各位
Tonight's dinner is amazing, folks:
钓到的鲯鳅
line-caught mahi mahi.
当地的渔民都是子承父业
The local fishermen pass the lines down from father to son,
所以你能体会到家族的传承
so, boy, you can taste the heritage.
我的老天
Dios mío!
怎么了
Eh, what?
大家好啊
Oh. Hey, guys.
我们在海滩碰到了这群超棒的猴子
We met these awesome monkeys on the beach,
我们说了只要它们足够搞笑
and we said they could crash here
就让它们暂住在这儿
in exchange for them being hilarious.
亲爱的  你都没告诉我
Sweetie, you did not tell me
你的妹夫是个这么有趣的人
your brother-in-law was such a fun guy.
你们俩应该开心才是
You two should be so happy.
你老公和你女朋友是好朋友
Your husband and your girlfriend are amigos!
你和谁在一起呢  金宝
Who's that with you, Jimbo?
那是史黛西吗
Is that Stacy?
天哪
Oh, my God.
金宝出轨了
Jimbo is cheating on me!
什么
Wha...?
好了  化妆套装  自拍杆
Ok. Make-up kit. Selfie stick.
老天  自拍杆充电器去哪了
Oh, God, where's the selfie stick charger?
亲爱的  没事
Honey, relax.
瀑布的照片肯定会不错的
The waterfall picture's going to be fine.
还不错  如果照片只是"不错"
Fine? If this photo is just "Fine,"
我们就离婚吧
we're getting a divorce.
好吧  好吧  这话过分了
Okay, okay, that crossed the line,
不过这是一生中仅此一次的旅行
but this is a once-in-a-lifetime trip
也是我们唯一记录完美瞬间的照片
and our only shot at a perfect moment.
我懂了  你是在为猴子派对的事情生气
I get it-- you're mad about my awesome monkey party.
但是你希望我对帕蒂的女朋友友善一点
But you wanted me to be nice to Patty's girlfriend,
而且你知道吗  她人很好
and guess what. She's cool.
正是你想要的  又一个酒友
Just what you need, another drinking buddy.
向我保证接下来的旅行你会规矩点就行了
Just promise me you'll behave for the rest of the trip.
好吧  好吧  我会离帕蒂那个
Okay, okay. I will stay far away
有趣的南方女朋友远远的
from Patty's fun Southern girlfriend.
或者就像她所说的
Or as she would say,
"比一个满脸肉的胖小子
"Further away than a fat-cheeked boy
离一走廊的老太婆还要远"
from a porch full of grannies."
快跑  胖小子  快跑
Run, fat boy, run!
你怎么这么紧张
Why are you freaking out?
你不是应该在丛林里亲吻大蟒蛇什么的吗
Shouldn't you be in the jungle kissing a boa constrictor or something?
这趟旅行太昂贵了  可爸妈压根不在乎
This trip is so expensive, and Mom and Dad don't care,
所以我在练习在车里睡觉
so I'm practicing sleeping in a car
为的是我们没房子住之后得睡在车里
for when we lose the house and have to sleep in our car!
苗浩斯的爸爸在他那本账本上
Well, Milhouse's dad writes down
记下了每个人欠他多少钱
how much money everyone owes in that book,
所以我们把那账本弄到手就行了
so all we have to do is snag it,
然后给爸妈看看他们欠了多少
then show Mom and Dad the numbers.
没错  让他们从金钱的疯狂中清醒过来
Yes! That'll snap 'em out of their financial insanity.
你准备好搞点小破坏和小入侵了吗
You up for a little breaking and entering?
入侵大人的卧室吗
Break into a grown-up's bedroom?
这可是大动作
Whoa, big move.
好吧  等大家去爬山的时候我们就动手
Okay, we'll do it when everyone's on the hike.
但是我们要怎么摆脱苗浩斯呢
But how do we get rid of Milhouse?
别担心  苗浩斯已经跟我绝交
Not a problem. Milhouse already ditched me
转头缠上希伯特医生的孩子了
for Dr. Hibbert's kid.
他的"度假伙伴"
His "Vacation friend."
JJ  你还喜欢玩乐高吗
Hey, JJ, do you still like Legos?
-不太喜欢了  -我也不喜欢
- Uh... not really. - Me neither.
乐高太差劲了
Lego sucks!
JJ  要不我们今晚给大人表演吧
Hey, JJ, why don't we put on a play for the grown-ups tonight?
哥斯达黎加的花
宝贝  你看  有个"哥斯达黎加的花"寻宝游戏
Ooh, sweetie, look, a "Flowers of Costa Rica" scavenger hunt.
我们一起能找到多少个呢
I wonder how many we can find together?
快点编  爸爸
Just braid, Daddy!
我得看起来超级性感才能赢回金宝的心
I need to look super hot to win back Jimbo's heart.
亲爱的  很多情感你都是第一次经历
Darling, you're experiencing so many emotions for the first time.
这很好  但是...
And that's very healthy, but...
他是因为你才搞外遇的
He strayed because of you!
JJ  有一次我朋友弄了个临时的纹身
Hey, JJ, one time my friend got a temporary tattoo
但跟他爸爸说是真的
but told his dad it was real.
好了  我们去偷账本吧
Okay, let's steal that ledger.
那是什么
What's that thing?
用帕蒂带钢圈的内衣做的抓升钩
Grappling hook made of Patty's underwire bra
还有爸爸浴袍的腰带
and Dad's bathing suit drawstring.
够得着吗
Will it reach?
在别的大人的卧室里待着感觉好奇怪
This is so weird, being in another grown-up's bedroom.
最强肌肉  猩猩泵感
猛兽臀肌  亢奋血管
我的孩子  我的废物
学着去爱一个让你失望的人
超强利帕
强效口唇疱疹乳膏
强力配方
老天  我正想说  他压根都不健身
Boy, you're telling me. He doesn't even work out.
我不想知道关于这家人的任何事了
Uh, I don't want to learn anything else about this family.
太迟了
It's too late.
好了  喝口水休息一下
All right, bottled water break.
我可以喝点溪水
I can drink from the stream.
经过这么多年  我肠胃的生物群落
After all these years, my gut biome is simpatico
已经和这里的细菌和谐共处了
with the local bacteria.
老天爷  有东西在我肚子里动
Ugh! Oh, God, there's something moving inside me!
让开  快让开
Oh, look out! Oh, look out!
快让开  我说了让开
Look out, I said look out! Look out!
不和睦  一点也不和睦
Oh, God, no simpatico! No simpatico!
侯默  想来一口吗
Hey, Homer. You want a hit off this?
伊芙琳  我们都爱在白天偷偷喝酒
Oh, Evelyn. You and I both love secret day drinking,
但我已经答应马姬在剩下的日子里
but I promised Marge I'd have a bad time
都要玩得不开心
the rest of this vacation.
我完全懂
I hear exactly what you're saying.
你找到账本了吗
Did you find the ledger?
没  但快看这个
No, but take a look at this.
这是已经灭绝的
These are stone spheres
哥斯达黎加迪奎斯人做的石球
made by the extinct Diquis people of Costa Rica.
没人知道它们的用处  但它们价值连城
No one knows what they were for, but they're priceless artifacts.
为什么苗浩斯的废柴爸爸有这些
So what is Milhouse's loser dad doing with them?
我对不起你  小肚肚
Oh, I'm sorry, Kirk's tum-tum.
爸比喝了些恶心水水
Daddy drank some ick-ick.
要开始咕咕叫了
Oh, the rumblies are coming.
The rumblies are coming!
来了
They're here!
如果这张照片拍得好
If we get this photo right,
这次多家庭旅行花的每一分钱都值了
this multi-family vacation will be worth every penny.
你控制欲爆表的样子真可爱
You're so cute when you're super controlling.
你喝酒了
You've been drinking.
说不定是伊芙琳在我的水里
Well, maybe Evelyn added
加了点南方风情的迷人液体
a little Southern charm to my water.
那个女人  她完全激发了你最坏的一面
That woman! She brings out the worst in you!
快看
Look!
天呐
Oh, my God.
太完美了
It's perfect.
你看起来很好  我看起来更好
You look good, and I look better.
快发  快发
Post it. Post it.
侯默
Homer!
兄弟  快看我做萨凡纳臭鼬翻滚
Buddy, hi. Watch me do a Savannah Polecat Flip.
不
No!
快回来  你这条吃相机的鱼
Come back, camera fish!
我只想要朋友们嫉妒我
All I wanted was for my friends to be jealous of me.
希望你现在满意了
I hope you're happy
你们家的秃头猩猩成功把我家女友拉低到了
now that that bald gorilla has dragged my girlfriend down
他的悲惨水准
to his pathetic level.
帕翠西娅·玛丽菲森·布伟业
Patricia Maleficent Bouvier,
你批评我丈夫这么多年  我都忍了
I've put up with you criticizing my husband for years,
现在我受够了
and I've had it.
伊芙琳灌醉了侯默
Evelyn got Homer drunk.
伊芙琳毁了我的梦想照片
Evelyn ruined my dream photo.
她才是负面影响
She's the bad influence.
胡说八道
That's ridiculous.
她也许是南方人  也许是女的
She may be Southern, she may be a woman,
但是承认吧  你的对象是个侯默
but you're dating a Homer.
完了个蛋
Oh, no.
妈  快看我在范浩腾的房间里发现的
Mom, look what I found in the Van Houtens' room!
他们在走私古代文物回国然后出售
They are smuggling these artifacts home to sell!
这就是为什么他们有钱来旅游
That's how they can afford this vacation.
但我们没这么多钱
But we can't.
我们将不得不住在车里
And we're gonna have to live in our car,
可是我们的汽车座椅黏糊糊的
and the seats in our car are sticky,
尽管是布做的
even though they're cloth!
你  你好恶心
You're... you're so gross.
太恶心了
It's so gross.
盐  以及胡椒粉
Salt... and pepper.
这些本来该是
These souvenirs were supposed to be
旅行结束之后给你们的纪念品
our end-of-multi-family-vacation gift to you all.
惊喜都毁完了
Way to spoil the surprise.
不"纯生"
Not very pura vida.
太不"纯生"了
Not very pura vida at all.
我已经和史黛西拜拜了
Stacy and I are finished.
肖娜·丘墨士  你愿意嫁给我吗
Shauna Chalmers, will you marry me?
天呐
Oh, my God!
金宝求婚了
Jimbo proposed!
我们他妈的要结婚了
We are getting freaking married!
你们倒是急着要走
Ooh, You guys are sneaking off early.
不考虑一起高空滑索  再多搞些破坏吗
Don't you want to come ziplining and ruin the trip some more?
我同意
Well, I would...
我老婆的意见  我们离开比较好
like to agree with my wife that it's better we leave.
我把账单给你  把钱算清
I'll give you the final bill now so we can settle up.
早退也不会打折
No discount for leaving early either.
我虽然信仰"纯粹的生活"  但也不傻
I may be mucho pura vida, but, uh, I'm not a sucker.
丽莎是对的
Lisa was right.
我们真的付不起
We really couldn't afford this trip.
真是一笔巨款
Ooh, that's a big number.
帕蒂怎么样了  一直都没看见她
How's Patty? I haven't seen her.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
她和我分手了
She... broke up with me.
妈  我知道你感觉不好
I know you feel bad, Mom,
但那位女士可是个侯默
but the lady is a Homer.
这么多钱
Oh, all that money,
我们甚至连照片都没照到
and we didn't even get the picture.
看看这个
Look at this.
范浩腾先生甚至收了盐罐
Mr. Van Houten even charged us
和胡椒罐的钱
for those salt and pepper shakers.
他之前说是给我们的礼物
He said those were a gift.
然后甚至都没有赠与这个动作
And he didn't even give them to us.
那没有拿到礼物我们是不会走的
Then we're not leaving without them.
这就解释清楚了
Oh, so that explains it.
找到你了
Gotcha.
你甚至不能让我们安静地玩个索道吗
Can't you let us even zipline in peace?
看看我们找到了你卧室里藏的什么宝贝
Look what we found hidden in your bedroom.
是探索者柯克艾德莫斯·范浩腾的画像
This is a portrait of explorer Kirkedemious Van Houten,
为一家荷兰饼干贸易公司平定了此地
who settled this area for a Dutch cracker-trading company,
他建造了这幢房子  现在还是你家的财产
and he built this house, which your family still owns.
你明明是免费得到的房子  却要让我们
You're charging us thousands of dollars in rent
付出上万元的租金
for a house you get for free.
范浩腾家欺骗了所有人
The Van Houtens are cheating all of us,
我们成了他们出去度假的经济基础
so we pay for their vacation.
-我很震惊  -我大吃一鲸
- I'm stunned. - I'm shocked.
我是肖娜
I'm Shauna.
我跟你们一样震惊
I'm just as surprised as any of you.
什么  拜托
Oh, what?! Come on!
这个骗局就是她的主意
This scam was her idea.
这一年她甚至变本加厉收钱
And this year she even charged you more
这样我们才能付得起"亲密教练"的钱
so we could pay for our "Intimacy coach."
一根羽毛到底能做多少事情呢
I mean, how many things can you do with a feather?
别着急  各位  别着急
Oh, easy, guys, easy.
大家都想保持纯粹的生活  对吧
Everyone try to remain pura vida. Huh?
如果你不还钱的话  我他妈要纯粹地
I'm gonna pura vida my foot in your ass
用脚给你菊花来一记暴击
if you don't give me back my money.
他要跑了
He's zipping away!
在他提走支票的钱之前抓住他
Stop him before he endorses those checks!
所以你跟伊芙琳分手了吗
So, you and Evelyn broke up?
我以为你真的很喜欢她呢
I thought you really liked her.
的确  但是多亏了你  我一直看到侯默
I did, but now all I see is Homer, thanks to you.
帕蒂  回来
Patty! Come back!
我不能  因为我在索道上
I can't! Because I'm on a zipline...
帕蒂  很抱歉我让你不开心
Patty, I'm sorry I upset you,
但是伊芙琳就是你的侯默
but Evelyn is your Homer,
没有别人会明白你为何爱着她
and no one else will ever understand why you love her,
除了你自己
except for you.
但是二者之间又有很大的不同
But there's one huge difference between them.
继续说
I'm listening.
伊芙琳爱你
Evelyn loves you,
而侯默简直恨死你了
and Homer hates you more than anything in the world.
他恨我的程度超过塞尔玛吗
Even more than he hates Selma?
他为塞尔玛感到惋惜
He feels sorry for Selma,
因为她必须跟你一起生活
because she has to live with you.
等等  伊芙琳
Hold on, Evelyn!
我来了
I'm coming!
给给  拿走你的钱
Go ahead, take your money.
拿走一个男人唯一的经济来源
Take away a man's only source of income.
不  真的很高端
No, it's real classy.
我们刚刚享受了一次免费旅行
We just got a free vacation.
万岁
Hooray!
现在让我们租用直升机回瀑布那里吧
Now let's charter a helicopter back to the waterfall
去照你妈妈珍贵的照片
to get your mom's precious picture.
不不不  没关系
No, no, no. It's okay.
旅行的意义不在于完美的照片
Vacations aren't about the perfect photo.
而是要活在当下  自由自在
It's about being in the moment and living your... vida.
他们真像地毯里的虫子那样可爱
They're as cute as two bugs in a rug.
巴仔恶魔
亲爱的  我只想让你知道
Honey, I just want you to know
金宝·琼斯是个很不错的年轻人
that Jimbo Jones is a fine young man,
我很乐见你们两个人结婚了
and I'm very happy for you two to be married.
-没错  -是的
- Truly. - Yeah...
金宝的父母惊慌失措取消了婚礼
Jimbo's parents freaked out and canceled the wedding.
无所谓
Whatever.
我很高兴有人设定了底线
I'm glad somebody's setting limits.
你知道  小可爱  我在尽力尝试
You know, pumpkin, I'm doing my best.
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
对于一个单身父亲来说  并不是那么容易
That as a single father, it's not always so easy
能够把指导和尊重平衡好
to balance guidance with respect for your...
是的
Yeah...
是的  现在我们有共鸣了  对吗
Yeah, now we're connecting, huh?
我们为什么不能走呢
Why can't we just leave?
因为我们得在彼得叔叔来之前打扫干净
'Cause we have to clean up before Uncle Pete gets here,
不然明年就不能来了
or we'll lose our week next year.
喂  这东西很贵的
Hey, hey, this stuff is expensive!
听到没
Comprende?
不行  朋友  不行
No, amigos, no, no.
不行  纯粹的生活
No, pura vida!
纯粹的生活
Pura vida!
不  不行
Oh, no! No bueno!